手术室里的一切都很紧张
It's intense what happens in the O.R.
当病人命悬一线
When live's on the line，
你像玩弄布丁那样拨弄着大脑
and you're poking their brains like they are silly pudding,
此时你需要同身旁的医生形成默契
be a firmer bond with the surgeons right next to you,
打不破而又难以言喻的默契
an unbreakable, indescribable bond.
此默契来源于亲密
It's intimate being tight together like that.
你们醒了吗
You're up?
-没有  -是的
- No.  - Yes.
不论你是否喜欢这种默契
Whether you like it or not,
无论你是否喜欢他们
whether you like them or not,
你们是一家人
you become family.
邪恶的女巫死了
The wicked witch is dead.
打比方还是真死了
Metaphorically dead or dead dead?
你们在说谁呢
Who are you talking about?
汉娜  她的名字从手术日程上消失了
Hahn. Her name is off the surgical board,
她的手术都取消了
Her surgery has been cancelled
我不知道原因  我只知道
I don't know how or why but I do know
汉娜走人了
Hahn is gone.
太糟了  她很有才华
It's too bad. She was really talented
你们不是在跟我说话吗
You are not talking to me?
格蕾在家吗
Is, uh, Grey home?
是的
Yes
死神  出来  你在哪  死神
Death?! Come on. Where are you, Death?
死神
Death?! Aah!
阎王  天哪  几百年没见了
Die! Oh, my god! It's been-- forever. Oh.
你看上去就像
Oh, wow. You look like...
-死神  -死神
- Death!  - Death!
那个穿睡衣的家伙是你男朋友吗
Is the guy in the pajamas your boyfriend?
-如果是的话  他太帅了  -是的
- Because if so, then hot. - Right?
你是哪位
Uh, hey. Uh... who are you?
我叫赛迪  你又是哪位
I'm Sadie. Who are you?
我  我叫克里斯蒂娜
I'm--I'm--I'm Cristina.
不用说  上医学院以前她们一定去
Apparently they went backpacking around Europe together or something...
欧洲旅行过之类的
before med school.
那女人就这样把我赶下了床
You know that woman all but kicked me out of the bed?
糟透了
That's terrible.
还有死神  她的小名不叫死神  而是梅
And death? Meredith's name is not death. It's Mer.
我很同情你
I really feel for you.
她以前连提都没提过这女人
You know, she's never even mentioned this woman.
她们之间能有多铁
I mean, how good of a friend can she be?
铁到把我们俩都赶下床
Good enough to kick us both out of bed.
欢迎来到我的世界
Welcome to my world.
这女人就是我当初进医学院的原因
This woman is the reason I went to med school in the first place.
我想如果连死神这样的懒鬼...
I figured if a slacker like death...
-都能挥舞手术刀  那我也能  -梅  梅
- could handle slicing people open, then I could, too. -Mer. Mer.
梅瑞狄斯可不是懒鬼
Meredith's not a slacker.
我可以给你爆点料
Ooh, I could tell you some stories.
你敢
But you won't.
塞迪  你推迟了住院实习期
So, Sadie, you postponed your residency
就为了能在停尸房工作
to work in a morgue?
是的  尸体随你怎么划  没有讨厌的规矩
Yeah, you know, a lot of the fun cutting, none of the rules,
但我后来厌倦了
But I got bored.
我开始渴望接触流动的鲜血
Started craving blood that was flowing.
你现在来到这里  不敢相信你来了
And now you're here. I can't believe you're here.
伊兹  你不进去吗
Iz, you coming?
进去  只是我还要等一会儿
Yeah. I just need a minute.
我明白  汉娜的病人勾起你对丹尼的回忆
Look, I get it. Hahn's case brought up the Denny thing.
但汉娜已经不在这儿了
But Hahn's not even here anymore.
已经成为过去式了
It's stuff from the past.
已经过去了  伊兹
Stuff from the past, Iz.
你不明白
You don't understand.
我能明白
I might...
只要你肯告诉我
if you'd talk to me.
算了
Fine.
回头见
See you inside.
我在走着
I'm walking.
早上好
Morning.
一个人朝前走着
Walking straight ahead, all by myself.
你看上去很美  有点疲惫  但是很美
You know, you look good. Tired, but good.
我说过你的短发挺迷人的吗
Did I mention I find the short hair kind of sassy?
我再一次走过这个角落  一个人
Now I'm turning this corner, again, all alone.
这些...是我的小猫抓的
These are s--uh, scratches from my kitten.
它就爱到处乱抓
He's a crazy scratchy scratcher.
你养猫吗
You're a cat person?
其实我指的是梳子
I meant hairbrush.
我的梳子很容易抓伤手的
It--it--I have a crazy scratchy hairbrush.
我的主刀手术已经危在旦夕了  三号
Solo surgeries are at stake here, three.
你不能这样古古怪怪的也不能受伤
I can't have you acting weird or wounded.
我状态很好  真的
I'm--I am on top of my game. Really.
去整形科  离我远远的  走吧
I'm sending you to plastics, far, far away. Just go.
你知道一个心脏科的家伙吗  叫狄克逊
Hey, what do you know about a heart guy named Dixon?
狄克逊不是"家伙"  她叫维吉尼亚 狄克逊
Dixon? Uh, no, not a guy. I've heard of Virginia Dixon.
专业水平超高  人却很低调  等一下
She's got an incredible record. Really low mortal-- Wait.
-她要来这儿吗  -是的  就今天
- Is she coming here?  -Yeah. Today.
背部心脏移植  我也参加的
Piggyback heart transplant. I'm on the case.
什么  为什么没我的份
What? What? W-why am I not on the case?
她是你的前任克里斯蒂娜
So she's your pre-Cristina Cristina?
你得告诉我为什么她叫你死神
You gonna tell me why she calls you death?
死神和阎王的故事  天机不可泄露
Oh, No. The adventures of death and die are better left untold.
你妹妹在她的小细胳膊上切丝儿
Hey, pedia's julienning her skinny little chicken arms,
另外 目前还是不明了H为何不翼而飞
And still no word on what made "h" hitch a ride with her flying monkeys.
-回见  -翻译给我听
- Later.  - Translate that for me.
莱西可能在偷偷拿自己练刀
Lexie may be a secret cutter,
还有  汉娜辞职的原因也不了
and there's still no word on why Hahn quit.
是真的吗  莱西的事?
Is that true, about Lexie?
我不知道  我怎么会知道
I don't know. How would I know?
-如果是真的你会怎么做  -什么都不做
- If it's true, what are you gonna do about it?  - Nothing.
梅瑞狄斯  你不能袖手旁观  她是你妹妹
Meredith, you can't do nothing. She's your sister.
那又怎样
And?
你们是一家人
And you're family.
我不明白
I'm not understanding.
莱西是你的家人
Lexie is your family.
算了
Forget it.
嗨  亨特医生
Hello, Dr. Hunt.
杨医生
Dr. Yang.
谢谢
Thank you.
病人什么情况
Hey, what do we got?
挤压受伤  几分钟后就到
Uh, crush injuries. Couple minutes out.
你知道汉娜是怎么回事吗
Hey, w-what do you know about Hahn?
她走了
Um, she's gone.
-可是为什么  -我不知道
- Yeah, but why?  - I don't know.
你们可是朋友啊
You two are friends.
我不想谈这个  好吗
I don't want to talk about it, okay?
只想来点大出血  内脏  骨头错乱
I want blood and guts and mangled bones.
最好是重伤  花一整天才能治好的那种
I want a guy so badly smashed up, it takes all day to fix him.
我想做一场惊天动地的手术  不想谈汉娜
I want to rock a surgery. I don't want to talk about Hahn.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
无名氏  花了很久才把他弄出车子
Unidentified man with prolonged extrication time.
得把他从工作中的垃圾车里吊出来
They had to fish him out of a working garbage truck.
多处挤压伤  开放性骨折  昏迷指数3级
Multiple crush injuries, open fractures, G.C.S. 3,
-我们没法把他解开  -解开?
- and we couldn't unhook him in the field.  - Unhook him?
他的股骨断成2节  刺入了自己的躯干
His femur's broken in half, and it's puncturing his torso.
他被钉住了
He's impaled.
被自己钉住了
Impaled on himself?
人肉麻花儿
Human pretzel.
这个不错
That'll do.
检查腘动脉搏动
Check his popliteal pulse.
感觉不到搏动
I'm getting nothing.
因为他的膝盖在这儿
That's because his knee is over here.
你觉得他当时正在垃圾车里睡觉
You think he was sleeping in that dumpster and
正好他们开始碾垃圾
they started crushing the trash?
真够衰的
That's a bad day.
我来了  我错过什么了吗
Hey, I'm here. What did I miss?
好吧  你今天是第一天来
Okay, it's your first day.
你还是站在一边安静的看着吧
Why don't you just stand back and shut up?
双肺呼吸音清晰平均  不敢相信
Breath sounds are clear and equal, both sides. Unbelievable.
说明没有刺到肺部
So no punctured lung.
需要做便携X光以及超声探伤
We need a portable X-Ray and an ultrasound.
有人呼我们
Someone paged us.
-我呼的  -你呼的  真稀罕啊
- I did.  - You did? That's a first.
这也很稀罕
So is this.
我见过很多外伤患者  断胳膊断腿的
I've seen a lot of trauma-- guys cut in half, amputations,
内脏掉出来的  但我从来没见过这样的
eviscerations-- but I have never seen anything like this.
我想你们也许能帮上忙
I wondered if you could help.
我们排名12  本应拿到第一再招人的
You hire when you're number 1, not number 12.
但我今天需要你当一次公关
But I need you to be my ambassador today.
向狄克逊医生展示西雅图圣恩医院的精髓
Show Dr. Dixon what Seattle Grace is all about.
我花了很多钱
I've thrown a lot of money,
给了她一个职位以及一大笔研究经费
a big title and a lot of research dollars at her.
-但...  -但是什么
- But...  - But what?
她有点怪
Um... she's a little different.
她的情绪有些低落
She's a little off.
所以我们今天得求她来  贝利
So we're wooing today, Bailey.
我会尽力求她的
I can woo with the best of 'em.
怎么  这个狄克逊精神不正常吗
So, what, Dixon is a nut job?
你说什么
Excuse me?
我只是说  我已经受够了医院里的疯子了
I'm just saying, I've already had my quota of crazy for the year.
我也有低落的时候  你想评判我吗
Hey, I've had my off days. You want to judge me?
你还没见过这女人  克莱夫
You never even met the woman, Karev.
你听到主任说的了
Now you heard the chief.
我们的任务是打动狄克逊医生
Our job is to impress Dr.Dixon today,
所以表现得好点
so be impressive.
给狄克逊医生看的表格准备好了
I've got the chart for Dr. Dixon.
我准备好工作了  而且很兴奋
I'm ready to work. I'm excited.
-别  她不上 -克莱夫
-Don't be. She's off. -Karev.
你还好不
You okay?
还好
Yeah.
好了  注意点  她来了
All right. Heads-Up. Here she comes.
迪克逊医生  你好
Oh, Dr. Dixon. H-Hi.
欢迎来到西雅图圣恩医院
Welcome to, uh, Seattle Grace.
很高兴你能来这工作
We're very happy to h-have you here.
-我  我是贝利医生 -我把我的工作服带来了
-I'm--I'm Dr. Bailey. -I-I brought my own lab coat.
我今天来是做心脏移植手术的
I'm here to perform a heart transplant today.
我是心脏科的
I do hearts.
由克丽斯提娜 巴纳德在1967年创造的科
A procedure invented by Christiaan Barnard in 1967.
我是心脏科的
I do hearts.
我是理查德·韦伯医生  我们在电话里交谈过
Uh, i--I'm Dr. Richard Webber. We spoke on the phone.
克莱夫  你带蒂克逊去最新的实验室
Karev, would you get Dr. Dixon the latest labs?
斯蒂文斯  介绍一下病人情况
Stevens, let's prep the patient, please.
好吧  她是有点怪怪的
Okay, then. She's a little off.
他的大腿骨除了插在身体里的那段
His femur's in pieces, I mean,
其他的都粉碎了
Except for the part that's stuck in his torso.
我没办法保住那条腿了
There's no way I'm saving that leg.
刺穿的部位正好在他的锁骨下
It looks like the impaled piece is lodged under his clavicle.
颈椎弯曲度还好  但没照过CT很难下定论
C-Spine looks clear. Without a C.T, it's hard to be sure.
那为什么做不了CT扫描呢
And why can't we get a C.T. Scan?
他刺穿的地方很难看清楚
The way he's impaled, it's hard to get a clear reading.
你可知道现在问问题是很白痴的
You know, there is such a thing as a stupid question.
同志们  我们的机会很小
Guys, guys, we have a very limited window here, okay?
站那去
Stand over there.
器官处于这种状态  几小时之后...
With vitals like these,In a few more hours...
他的身体根本承受不了手术了
His body won't be able to withstand surgery at all.
幸运的是他毫无知觉
Good thing he's unconscious.
不把大腿骨拿出来  我们什么都做不了
Well, we can't do anything till we dislodge the femur from his clavicle.
好了  那就把它拔出来
Okay, then let's unimpale him.
杨  格蕾还有新来的  摁住他肩膀  把他绑紧点
Yang, Grey, new kid, hold his shoulders. Brace him hard.
-我握住他的脊椎 -我摁住他身体
-I'll hold his c-Spine. -I got his torso.
我得把后臀的脱臼部位归位
I need to guide the posterior hip dislocation.
这条腿一拿出来
The second that leg is out,
确保要持续加压停止出血
Be ready to assert pressure to stop the bleeding.
-知道了没 -比在尸体旁工作好多了吧
-Got it? -Better than working on corpses, huh?
数三下  一...
On the count of three. One...
二...
Two...
三
Three.
大腿骨肯定卡在里面了
Femur's really wedged in there.
好吧  我拉的时候直接把身体向前推
Okay, push directly on the clavicle while I pull.
好了  就差一点了  还差一点  稳住
Okay, almost there. Almost there. Steady.
再来一点点
Just a little bit further.
斯隆  我需要你  把他的膝盖转向我右边
S-Sloan, I need you to, um, rotate his knee to my right.
推10品克吗啡进去  现在!
Push 10 of morphine now!
-抬上来  上来  -伸进去  保持压力
-Up, up, up, up. -Just get in there and hold the pressure.
好了  把他腿骨稳固住  放在他身边
Okay, get his femur stabilized and down by his side.
赶快  压住
Hurry! Hold pressure.
伸进去  快啊
Get in there. Come on. Aah!
尸体可不会这样
Corpses don't do that.
-先生  你得冷静下来 -你们在对我做什么啊
-I need you to calm down, sir. -What are you doing to me?
-能告诉我你名字么  先生 -从我眼前消失  把手拿开
-Sir, can you tell us your name? -Get out of my face! Get your hands off!
-你们弄疼我了 -照他说的做  每个人把手拿开
-You're hurting me! -Do as he says. Hands off, everybody.
把手拿开
Hands off.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
帝莫西 米勒
Timothy Miller.
米勒先生  我们得给你做手术
Mr. Miller, W-We need to get you into surgery.
我能走了是不是  我能走了
I'm gonna be able to walk, right? I gotta be able to walk.
现在  我们只是在设法让你活下来
Right now, we're just trying to keep you alive.
我们的心外科室很宽敞
Our cardiac wing is extensive and
-里面的设备都... -第一个成功
-Well-Equipped with all of... -The first successful
移植心脏的手术  是在1896年9月7日  是由
Heart transplant was performed on september 7, 1896, by Dr.
路德维格医生在德国的法兰克福完成的
Ludwig Rehn, frankfurt, germany.
是的
Okay.
很抱歉  我得打断你们
Uh, excuse me. I don't mean to interrupt.
请打断  我的意思是  你向
Uh,Please inter...I mean, just, please update Dr.
迪克逊医生汇报病人的新情况吧
Dixon on the patient.
斯蒂文斯医生在为移植手术做准备
Dr. Stevens is prepping your transplant patient for surgery.
他们在六年前就安排了手术
They scheduled a transplant six years ago,
但心脏太小了
But the heart was too small,
所以他们额外的加了一个捐赠心脏
So they doubled up and added a donor heart
来帮助维持本身的心脏功能
To help his own heart function
-他们做了背负手术 -异位移植
-They did a piggyback -Heterotopic transplant.
背负手术通俗叫法
Piggyback is the colloquial name for the procedure.
别这么叫
Don't do that.
我们带你去见见这病人  怎么样
How about we... take you to meet the patient?
他们告诉我  这心脏本属于一个女孩的
They tell my heart belonged to a girl that
她在求搭便车的时候被车撞死了
Was hit by a car while she was hitchhiking.
现在我开车  总能看到搭便车的
And now when I'm driving, I see hitchhikers all the time
总是会见到她
Always up ahead
就在我前方  但我到了那儿
Just up ahead, but when I get up ahead,
他们又没了
They're gone.
你可不信他说的话  对吧
You're not buying any of this, are you?
我就不该要这个心脏
I should never have gotten the heart.
我不明白这心脏...
I-I don't understand how the heart...
纳瓦霍人  我们甚至都不去碰死尸
Navajos...We don't even touch the dead.
我们不碰他们的身体和财物
We don't touch their bodies or belongings
是因为还有灵魂在那
Because the spirit clings there.
把死人身体里的东西缝进我胸口  真是...
So to have part of a dead body sewed into my chest is...
我的朋友都是老封建
My friends who follow the old ways,
他们求我别这么做
They begged me not to do it.
我应该听他们的话的
I should've listened.
对不起  我不明白
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
你觉得你见鬼是因为这移植的心脏
You think you're haunted by your transplanted heart,
但你不还在这等新的移植呢嘛
But you're here for a new transplant.
不是  我正要告诉你这个呢
No! That's what I'm trying to tell you.
我不想要  我不要新的心脏
I don't want it. I don't want the new one.
我就想让你们把这个拿出来
I just want you to take the old one out.
等等  这简直太蠢了  拿着这个心脏  兄弟
Wait. That's just plain stupid. Take the heart, man.
既然人家给你了  你就拿着啊
Take the heart if they offer it.
他刚说他不要捐赠的心脏
Did he just say he doesn't want the donor heart?
是的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
克雷 比道尼  你有没有意识到  如果没有新的心脏
Clay bedonie, are you aware that without a new heart,
在突然而极其痛苦的死去之前
You'll live a short life attached to a
你只能依附机器活很短的时间
Machine before dying a sudden and agonizing death?
看见没  我就是说的这个
See, that--That's what I'm talking about.
每五次平滑针后缝合  然后交换
Five parallel pulley stitches per cut, then switch.
你确定我会不疼吗
You sure I'm numb?
疼就挺住
Toughen up.
当一个住院医生被选去参加主刀手术
When one of our residents gets picked for the solo surgery,
我们中的一个也能参加  这是我们的目标
One of us gets to scrub in, so we have a goal here.
-想着目标  -主刀手术  完全值得的
- Focus on the goal. Solo surgeries. - Totally worth it.
主刀手术  完全值得
Solo... surgeries. Totally worth it.
你们好
Hello, hello.
我需要人去跑几个地方  再去取X光片
I need someone to run these labs and pull these x-Rays, please.
会做的
Will do.
这地方看起来挺适合休息的嘛
Hey, this looks like a cool place to hang out.
你们在干什么呢
What are you guys doing?
这是给实习生的  是我们的地盘
This is for interns. It's--It's our hangout.
去找你们自己的
Go find your own.
对不起
Sorry.
主刀手术
Solo surgeries.
完全值得
Totally worth it.
要是不能走了  我就不活了
I don't want to live if I can't walk.
我们会竭尽全力来保你的腿
We'll do our best to save the leg
我是流浪者  我靠走路为生
I'm homeless. Walking is how I survive.
那是我能生存下来的方法
It's how I... get from one day to the next.
马里昂大街在早晨2点至6点是安全的
Marion street's safe from 2:00 to 6:00 a.M.
然后我走到半旗桥上
And then I go over the half-Mast bridge,
在那儿待到6点30  等车流多起来
And I hang there till 6:30 until the traffic hits.
然后我走到贝尔镇  在河边溜达
And then I go over to Belltown and hang out on the waterfront.
在河边的时候  要是不方便的话
And then the waterfront, if it's trouble,
我就回到第4街
Then I go back up to 4th street.
我是没家的人  我不能不走路
I'm homeless. I-I can't not walk.
我  我该怎么办  我该怎么办啊
I, What am I gonna do? What am I gonna do?
你的伤势很严重
Your injuries are critical.
如果我们不给你做手术的话
If we don't get you to surgery--
你们的手术能让我走路吗
Will your surgery make me walk?
那我就不做了
Then I don't want it!
好吧  可以
Okay. All right.
你们听到他说的了  手术取消
You heard the man. The surgery's off.
我很感激你能告诉我
I appreciate you trying to advise me to do
你认为的最好的
what you think is best.
那些是事实  不是建议
These are facts, not opinions.
我要说的是
What I'm saying is--
他想说的是  与其不安的活着
He's trying to say he would rather live a shorter life
不如少活些时候
That's unhaunted than a longer one that is.
我没说我同意  我只是...
I'm not saying I agree. I'm just...
我还是站那去好了
I'm just gonna stand over here.
好主意啊
That's a good idea.
心脏从我身体里拿出来之后
The heart that you take out of me,
会怎么处理
What happens to it?
拿去做病理  然后作为医疗废物处理掉
It goes from the O.R. to pathology to medical waste.
我得要回来  用它祭奠
I need that heart back for ritual.
我们要遵守法律  医院是有规定的
We have laws. There are rules.
规定就是规定
Rules are rules.
也许我们能折衷一下
Maybe there's a compromise to be made here.
或许我们可以  我不知道
Uh, we could, I don't know, uh,
给他放回原来的心脏  完成仪式
Give him back the old heart to do the ritual,
-同时新的心脏仍旧继续工作  -不
-Then give him a chance to live by still putting the new heart in.  -No.
不  这样行不通
No. It doesn't work that way.
还是会闹鬼的  会有新鬼出现
I will still be haunted, just by a new ghost.
我们有规章
There are rules.
我们有法律  还有规章  规不可破  法不可违
We have laws, and there are-- Rules are rules and laws are laws.
不行
No.
那么就这样
So that's it?
不手术  你就这么走开了
No surgery? You're just gonna walk away?
我是尊重病人的意愿
I'm respecting the patient's wishes.
病人还有伤  情况还不稳定
The patient's unstable with an open wound.
我们在处理啊
Which we are packing.
-病人就要死了  -你不能就这么一走了之
-This guy is circling the drain.  -You cannot just walk away.
-别插手我的急救室  -你的急救室
-Don't tell me how to run things in my e.R.  -Your e.R.?
我们救死扶伤
We save lives here.
我们才不草草处理病人  任他们去死
We don't just patch up patients and leave them to die.
如果你做不到
If you can't handle that,
滚回你的沙漠去  这里有我们就够了
Go back to the desert and leave us here to do our jobs.
托瑞斯医生
Dr.Torres,
请告诉我  你能找到办法给他双腿
Please tell me you can figure out some way to build this man some legs.
右股骨骨折了
Well, the right femur's toast.
还有臀部和半个骨盆也是
So is the hip and half the pelvis,
但是如果我在这放些钢钉  这里放个钢板
But if I put some pins here and maybe a plate here...
我是说  这儿有些可利用的骨碎片
I mean, there are some viable bone fragments.
-我们并不是无从下手  你怎么想  -很大胆
-We're not starting from nothing. What do you think?  -I think it's wild.
-行了吧  她没问你  -她才第一天上班
-All right, she wasn't talking to you.  -It's her first day.
能不能不要这么
Could you not be so..
不  她是实习生  她要明白自己的地位
Could you not be so-  -No, she's an intern. She needs to learn her place.
我觉得这需要很多的硬件
I think it's a lot of hardware.
这个男的需要的是一条全新的腿
What the guy needs is a whole new leg.
也许我能办到
Well, maybe I can do that.
没错  我的意思是  这像一个谜题
Yeah, I mean, it's kind of a puzzle.
我只需要弄明白我需要什么器械
I just need to figure out what
怎么样去完成
Equipment I need and--And how to pull it off.
-像积木  -那可比积木高科技多了
-Like lincoln logs.  -Uh, it's a little more high-Tech than that.
就是像积木一样
It's exactly like lincoln logs.
我需要你们帮我找来医院所有的钛金属
I need you guys to grab every piece of titanium we've got in the hospital.
我需要医院的规章制度来说明
Um. I need the hospital rules to specify the fact that we must
所有医生必须尊重病人的信仰
Respect all religious and spiritual beliefs of our patients.
规章
The rules?
没错  我在请求您发布这条部门规章
Yeah, I'm asking you to declare a rule of our department.
关于医生尊重病人信仰的规章
That we respect the beliefs of our patients?
-是的  -可那不是普遍的礼貌吗
-Yes.  -Isn't that just common courtesy?
-是的  -那我为什么要发布规章
-Yes.  -Then why am I declaring it?
迪克逊医生不具备这种礼貌  但是她信仰规章
Um... Dr. Dixon doesn't do common courtesy, but she understands rules.
所以如果有规章  就一切顺利
So if it's a rule, we're golden.
若没有  将出现一个发疯的病人  生气的医生
If not, we have a pissed-Off patient an apoplectic surgeon,
这些会毁掉一场成功的心脏手术
And none of those things makes for a successful
更别提拉拢狄克逊医生了
Procedure on a faulty heart, not to mention the failure to woo.
你希望我把这宣布为一条规章
You want me to announce it as a rule.
我就是目击证人  你只要举个右手
I'm here's a witness, you can maybe raise your right hand,
左手放到外科医生办公桌上  当参考书
Put your left one on the "physicians' desk reference."
那是一条规章
It's a rule.
谢谢
Thank you.
迪克逊医生  我是克里斯蒂娜·杨
Dr. Dixon, I'm Cristina Yang.
我是这里的住院医师
I'm a resident here,
我从实习生开始就专攻心脏科
And I've been focused on cardio since I began my internship.
我非常期待如果您能够
I'm certainly looking forward to anything that
其他人被调离这个案子了吗
-You might-  - Were the other ones taken off my case?
什么其他人
Oh, uh, what other ones?
那个黑人  男的  金发的
The black one, the male one, the one with yellow hair.
据我所知没有
Not that I'm aware of.
那你干嘛和我说话
Then why are you talking to me?
翰医生到底怎么了
S-- What happened to Hahn?
无论发生了什么  一定有个原因吧
Wh-Whatever made Hahn leave, it can be fixed.
除非  除非她被炒鱿鱼  她没有被炒吧  不是吗
U-Unless she a was fired. She wasn't fired, was she?
-她不会回来了  -你怎么会知道
-She's not coming back.  -You don't know that.
她确实知道
She kinda does.
怎么会
How?
因为她不
Because she doesn't...
看  这只是太
Look, it's just too...
我们吵架了
We had a fight.
拜托  梅瑞狄斯和我经常吵架
Oh, please. Meredith and I fight all the time.
我们还是一起工作
We still work together.
翰又不是你女朋友什么的
It's not like Hahn was your girlfriend or something.
天啊
Oh, my god.
她是你的女朋友
She was your girlfriend?
听着  我们还没
Look, we hadn't...
确认这段关系
Figured it all out.
等等  那么你现在是个拉拉了
Wait, so are you a lesbian now?
我不知道  也许你就拉拉过一回
I don't know. Maybe you were a once-Bian.
或者两回  管它呢  反正结束了
Or a twice-Bian. Whatever. It's over.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
她没事  别烦她
She's fine. Leave her alone.
我发现钛金矿了
I hit the titanium mother lode.
拜托  认真的吗
Oh, come on. Really?
莱西
Hey, Lexie.
最近怎么样
How are you?
一切顺利吗
Is, uh, everything going okay?
为什么问  有人说什么了吗  说我怎么样了吗?
Why, did somebody say something, like I was doing something?
不  我只是  你知道的
No, I'm just, uh, you know, as, uh,
我是以一个亲人的角度关心你
I'm asking as a person who's sort of related to you
最近有没有什么烦心事
if there's anything bothering you--
这么说这完全不是老板或住院医生或上级
So this is completely not as a boss or a resident or a superior keeping an eye
监视我作为一个学员在医院的表现
On what I do as a student in this program?
不不  我只是个有爱心的人  我只是想知道
No, no, I'm just a compassionate person, and I'm just wondering
你是否已经将悲伤痛苦转化为个人残缺
if you're channeling your tragic pain into, uh, self-Mutilation.
-你是个能自残者吗  -不
-Are you a secret cutter?  -No.
小格蕾  托瑞斯医生在创造
Little Grey, Torres is, uh,
一项在病人身上使用最多钛条的世界纪录
Trying to set a world record for most titanium rods used in one patient.
参加吗
You in?
小格蕾
Little Grey?
小格蕾  大格蕾
Little Grey. Big Grey.
这是我区分你们两个的方式
That's how I tell you two apart.
好的  我参加  我马上就来
Yeah, I'm in. I'll just be a minute.
你的人就不能让我安静的死去吗
Can't you people let a guy die in peace?
你的器官在衰竭
Your, uh, vitals are slipping.
我不会向你撒谎  这很糟糕
I'm not gonna lie to you. That's not good.
我遇到过更糟的
I been through worse.
是的  我可以想象到
Yeah, I imagine you have.
别这样
Oh, don't get like that.
别像在看一个有着神秘过往的悲剧英雄
Don't look at me like I'm some tragic hero with a secret past.
你是有故事的人
You have a story.
我们都是有故事的人
We all have a story.
我的生活发生了转折
I took a turn in my life.
我却连接不上
And I couldn't connect.
我迷失了
I lost...
我连接不上
I couldn't connect.
我的生活  一转折
My life, it took a turn and...
我就回不去了
And I just couldn't turn it back.
伙计们  我们需要关门几天
Guys, we need to shut down for a few days.
有人开始怀疑我们了
People are starting to get suspicious.
有人问我是不是自残
I was accused of being a secret cutter.
那就穿长袖衣服
So wear long sleeves.
我没发现我们邀请了新人加入
Oh, I didn't realize we were inviting more people here.
你在开玩笑吗  实习生的秘密小社会
Are you kidding? A secret intern society?
我对这个可没兴趣
I'm all over that.
我仍然觉得我们应该少冒险
Well, I still think we need to take fewer risks.
少冒险
Fewer risks?
拜托  门口有人把守
Come on. You got a guard at the door.
现在给三处伤口缝合使用局部麻醉
You're using more local anesthetic for three
接下来你就可以晋升去做胸管了
Sutures than you would upstairs for a chest tube.
听着  我知道你们这么做是为了练技术
Look, I get that you're doing all this to learn new skills,
但是如果放不开胆  你也就能学到这么多
But you're only gonna learn so much by being careful.
事实上  我不同意
Uh, actually, I would disagree.
我觉得唯一安全的方法
I think the only safe way to...
谁想帮我缝合
Who wants to stitch me up?
-你要告诉我死神和阎王的故事了吗  -不
-Are you gonna tell me about death and die?  -Nope. B
但是我为了你和莱西讲话了噢
But I did talk to Lexie for you.
-现在我需要你为我做点事  -什么事
-And now I need you to do something for me.  -What's that?
我要你去警告马克  让他的小斯隆离小格蕾远点
I need you to tell Mark to keep his little Sloan out of little Grey.
他勾引你
Is he hitting on you?
不  不是我的小格蕾  是莱西的小格蕾
No, not my little Grey. Lexie's little Grey.
我不清楚她发生了些什么
I don't know what's going on with her,
但她最不需要的就是斯隆和她上床
But the last thing she needs is Sloan going all man-Whore on her.
-所以你要去警告他离小格蕾远点  -好的
-So you need to tell him to step away from little Grey.  -All right.
我会尽力而为
I'll see what I can do.
小格蕾  德里克  小格蕾
Little Grey, derek. Little Grey.
她有没有
Did she, uh...
向你告别
She say good-Bye to you?
没
Nope.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我看起来像没事吗
Do I look okay?
我觉得还行啊
You look great.
那我还好
Then I'm okay.
看来...
So...
需要9天时间  做祭奠以摆脱心魔?
There's a 9-Day ritual to undo a haunting?
应该从9日祭奠开始
It starts with a 9-Day ritual.
你真的要浪费9天时间来干这事吗
Are you really gonna waste nine days on this?
-斯蒂文斯医生  -怎么了
-Dr. Stevens. -Yes.
为什么你对魔鬼的事这么感兴趣
Why are you so interested in my haunting?
能否...
Can...
能否让魔鬼来...
Can ghosts do things...
让他们来你身边干点什么
I mean, can they make things happen in your life?
我有两个病例联系到一起了
I've had two cases with two patients in a row
他们让我想起了我去世的未婚夫
that have really reminded me of my dead fiance
他也是做L-vad心脏移植手术  魔鬼能否帮我
Heart transplants and l-Vads and, Could he be doing that?
帮我把他们带到我身边来
Could he be bringing them to me?
伊兹  别这样
Izzie, come on.
他现在就在这儿吗  你的心魔
Is he here right now, your ghost?
我不想这么问  但是...
I... I hate to ask, but...
你不希望我参与你的手术
Oh, you don't want me in your surgery.
不是我认为  你有什么问题
It's not that I think there's something wrong with you.
只是我不希望我手术室里  还有别的魔鬼
It's just I don't need any extra ghosts in my operating room.
米勒先生
Mr. Miller.
你就不能让我安静会儿吗
What do you have to do get a little peace and quiet here
你感到疲倦是因为你失血过多
The fatigue you're feeling is from the blood loss.
而你感到恶心  晕眩
The queasiness, the dizziness
是因为你正因失血  而慢慢走向死亡
It's because you're slowly bleeding to death.
-干嘛  你在吓唬他吗  -不
-What, are you trying to scare him? -No.
我要确定他究竟要自杀  还是在抗挣
Trying to ascertain whether he's suicidal or just defeated.
米勒先生  你在街上活下来了  我知道你很坚强
Mr. Miller, you survived in streets, I know you're a fighter
这不代表我很坚强
That doesn't make me a fighter.
运气好罢了
It makes me lucky.
你抗挣了多久  10年  20年
How long you been out there, 10 years, 20?
你不在监狱里  你也没死
You're not in jail, you're not dead.
那不是运气好  你是个智者
That's not luck. You're smart.
聪明点  好好善待你自己
You gotta be smart to take care of yourself on your own.
我想是的
I guess.
米勒先生  你这样拒绝动手术
This, what you're doing right now, Mr.Miller, refuse surgery
就很不明智
It's not smart.
离这儿不远有个康复中心
There's a rehab center not too far from here.
能用医疗保险  你可以去那里
Medicare takes care of it. You could stay there.
有吃有喝  睡得舒服
Food, bed, long as you need.
让我们做手术吧
Just let us operate.
做了手术  才能把问题解决
Let us operate, and we'll figure the rest out.
切开粘合层速度这么快
That's the fastest I've ever seen
我可是第一次见到
anyone dissect through adhesions
迪克逊医生  我们医院有个规定
Uh, Dr. Dixon, there is a rule
应当把切下的废弃器官留给病人
regarding giving medical waste to the patient.
蒂克逊医生
Dr. Dixon?
怎么了?
What?
我刚才说  我们医院有个官方的规定
Uh, I was just saying there is a rule, an official
非常明确的规定
very very specific rule,
如果病人基于某种原因
That in the event a patient asks for
比如与信仰或文化因素有关
their organ or body part back for any reason
想要回他们的器官或身体的某个部分
related to or involving their cultural beliefs,
我们必须尊重他们的意愿
we must respect that patient's wishes,
把器官还给病人
and return that organ to the patient.
这就是规定  我之前忘说了
That is the rule I forgot to tell you about.
要是我现在就把它拿到楼下病理科去
If I went down to pathology right now,
他们会知道这些规定吗
would they know about the rule?
主任会知道的
Oh, the chief would know.
是他定的  他发布的规定
Uh, it's his rule. He declared it.
规定就是规定
A rule's a rule.
克莱夫医生
Dr. Karev...
确保我们遵守了主任的规定
Make sure that we follow the chief's rule and
并在手术后把心脏还给病人
return the heart to the patient after the surgery.
我要继续工作了
I'm going back to work now.
钳子
Clamp.
他们拿出来的胶状物是什么东西啊
What the hell is that gooey thing they're taking out of him?
你又沉默了
Oh. The silent treatment.
那好吧  如果你要继续这样
Okay, if you're gonna be that way.
那我就...
I'll just, uh...
我就静静地站在边上
I'll just stand here and be quiet.
你看那个  那真的很恶心
Okay, but that... that is disgusting.
我以为你会安静会儿
I thought you were gonna be quiet.
你表现得好象不希望我在这里
You know, you're acting like you don't want me to be here.
你知道你死后  我每天都在期盼什么吗
You know what I've wished for every day since you've died
我乞盼能再见你一面
I've wished that I could see you again.
我宁可抛弃一切  都想见到你
I'd have given anything just to see you...
哪怕就一次
One more time.
这样看着你  却明知无法触碰你
Looking at you and knowing that I can't touch you,
是对我的折磨
it's hurting me.
伊兹  你可以触碰到我
Izzie, you can touch me.
这不是真实的你
You're not real.
你不可能真的重现
You can't be real.
这意味着我心理不正常  总之就是有问题
So that means that I'm sick or something is wrong with me,
我可不想这样
And I can't hope for that.
我
I...
我不想这样
I can't hope.
你不是真的
You're not real.
伊兹  我和你一样都是真实的
Izzie, I am as real as you
就像楼下那恶心的胶物一样真实
that gooey, disgusting thing down there.
碰一下我
Touch me.
伊兹  摸摸我
Izzie... touch me.
不
No!
你为什么要过来
Why are you here?
为什么
Why?
我为你而来  伊兹·斯蒂文斯
I am here for you, Izzie Stevens.
钳子
Clamp.
好了  就这样
Okay, that's it.
捐赠的心脏被分离了
The donor heart is separated.
旁通阀的套管准备好了
We have the cannulas ready for bypass.
下一步就做L-vad
Next step is the l-Vad.
咦  这是怎么了
Y--What--What is that?
这不对啊  不可能的
That's not right. That can't be happening.
他的心脏在跳动
His heart's beating.
他的心脏怎么自己跳起来了
How is his heart beating on its own?
不可能这样  也不应该这样啊
It... can't be happening. It shouldn't be happening.
他的心脏在动  他的心脏跳起来了
That heart is beating. That heart is beating.
不该跳动的  不该有心跳的
It shouldn't be beating. It sh-Shouldn't be beating.
我从未见过这样的重建手术
I've never seen a reconstruction like this.
我也从未做过这样的手术
Well, I've never done one like this.
只要有希望  就能实现
Here's hoping it works.
好了  杆子我准备好了
All right. I'm ready for the rod.
你们那里情况如何
How are you guys doing up there?
因捆绑造成的失血实在太多了
A lot of hemorrhaging, bleeding through the packing.
-试一下纤维密封剂  -谢谢提醒  谢博德医生
-Try the fibrin sealant. -Good call. Thank you, Dr. Shepherd
你的紫胶缝合做得怎样了  小格蕾
How you doing on that lac, little Grey?
挺好  正准备做下一个了
Good. Moving on to the next lac.
快结束了吗  我看看
You finished already? Let me see.
缝合得相当平滑
Wow. Pulley stitches.
做得不错啊
Nicely done.
谢谢  斯隆医生
Thank you, Dr. Sloan.
我的心脏怎样了
So my heart...
它开始自己跳动了
It started beating by itself.
如果继续保持这样的功能
If it continues to function like this,
你就不需要l-vad或其他起博装置了
You won't need an l-Vad or any other kind of machinery.
是个好消息
It's wonderful news.
实在是非典型
It's very atypical.
对我来说不是  我终于自由了
Not for me. I'm finally free.
不再被魔鬼缠身了
I'm not haunted anymore.
你的心脏休息了6年
Your heart had six years to rest, which is...
可能因此获得了自我修复
Probably enough time for it to repair itself,
所以才自己恢复了心跳功能
Which is why it started beating again.
我以前从未见过
I've never seen this before.
有过此类病历  却是首次亲眼见到
I've read about it, but I've never seen it before.
你有你的信仰  而我有我的
You have your beliefs. I have mine.
我没有信仰  我只信科学
I don't have beliefs. I have science.
科学就是信仰
Science is a belief,
是种能看得见  摸得着的信仰
a belief in only what you can see and touch.
而我的信仰更多
I believe in more.
我打断大家  看看进行得如何了
Just thought I'd stop in to see how everything's going.
我还差几个小时
Well, I'm still several hours away,
但我的确在实现突破
But I may actually pull this off--
重建他的骨骼
Rebuilding a man's skeleton from scratch.
同时我们也发现
And we just found out that, uh,
格蕾医生的缝合技术相当有进步
Dr.Grey here can out-Pulley stitch Shepherd.
说得我不好意思了
Oh, I wouldn't go so far as to say that.
干得好  格蕾医生
Excellent job, Dr. Grey.
杨医生  说明你教得也很好
And excellent job of teaching, Dr. Yang.
主任
Sir?
能花时间教你的实习医生
Taking the time to teach your interns,
让他们进步神速度
And they are retaining that knowledge.
我还没决定由谁首做主刀手术
I haven't made my decision yet on the solo surgery,
但如果你继续用心教
But you keep teaching like that,
我会关注你的
and you're my one to watch.
谢谢主任
Thank you, sir.
-心跳减弱  心率过低  -做心脏复苏
He's crashing. V-Fib. Start c.P.R.
电子显示器一档  电板360度
Push 1 of epi and charge the paddles to 360.
准备
Clear.
谢谢
Thank you.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
你们怎么处理死者的物件
So what do you do now with the haunted piece?
埋掉还是
Do you bury it or...
烧掉  由我们部落的巫师烧掉
Burn it. Actually, my tribe's medicine man will burn it.
焚烧时  我不能碰触到它的烟雾
I'm not allowed to even touch the smoke.
不接触
So does the not-Touching thing,
是指不接触身体还是
does that apply to just the flesh or-- No,
连死者的物品也不能碰
We don't touch their belongings.
我们会净化珠宝  勋章
We can cleanse jewelry, medals,
但织物  床单  衣服
but fabric, bedding, clothes,
还有死者的书
Books that were owned by the dead,
全部都烧掉
we burn all of it.
死者的亡灵可能附在上面
The spirit can cling to any of it.
天啊
Oh, No.
跟着你的灵魂
Your ghost...
你不是还留着他的东西吧
You still don't have anything of his, do you?
死亡时间19点22分
Time of death--19:22.
我给他做了新的腿骨
I built his bones.
你尽力了
You tried.
我们都尽力了
We all tried.
不  我不止尽力  我完成了
No, I didn't try. I did it.
我完成了任务  我做好了腿骨
I did my part. I built his bones.
我辛辛苦苦的做好了腿骨  而你们
I built his bones from scratch, and you...
你们该尽力保住他的命
All of you, you were supposed to keep him alive.
那是你们该做的
That is all you people had to do.
你们必须这么做
You just had to...
让他活着
Keep his body breathing.
让他好好的活着
You just had to keep him safe and--And
直到我把腿骨安好
Breathing and living until I made his bones.
我已经  我已经把腿骨做好了
I made... I made his bones...
要等我安进去
Until... until I made his bones.
我都做好了
I made his bones.
-我做好了  -你们先走
I made his bones. Why don't you guys go ahead,
我留下帮托瑞斯医生收拾
and I'll help Dr.Torres clean up?
-通知太平间  -知道了  走吧
Go call the morgue. We've got it. Go.
全部人出去
Everyone, clear out.
干得不错  狄克逊医生
Uh, excellent job today, Dr. Dixon.
不错  按规定办事
Excellent... rule following.
我只对一件事感兴趣  心脏
I only have one real area of interest--The human heart.
我热爱它  爱它有规律的跳动
I love it. I like its regularity.
我对它了解的一清二楚
I know everything there is to know about it.
我爱它  因为它可预测  它有规律
I like its predictability. It has rules.
每个心室有各自的功能
Every chamber has a function,
每个功能有各自的规律
every function has a movement.
我爱它的颜色  令人欣慰
I like the color. It's comforting.
你熟悉亚氏保加症吗  贝利医生
Are you familiar with asperger's syndrome, Dr. Bailey?
当然
Uh, of course.
社交功能严重受损
A significant impairment during social situations...
我不擅长讥讽挖苦别人
I'm not good at cues like sarcasm or condescension,
但我能看出别人在操控我
But I do know when I'm being manipulated,
能看出别人在取笑我
And I know when I'm being made fun of.
我不太喜欢这个医院
I don't think I like this hospital very much.
我一点都不喜欢这个医院
I don't think I like this hospital at all.
莱西·格蕾很厉害
that Lexie Grey sure knows
能熟练的缝针
how to wrap herself around a suture.
马克  梅瑞狄斯有点担心
Mark, Meredith has some concerns.
不是第一次了
Well, that's not news.
担心莱西
About Lexie.
莱西似乎  很脆弱
Apparently Lexie is...Fragile,
和上司有暧昧
and getting involved with a superior
会让她更脆弱  所以
might make her more fragile, So...
我只是说她的缝合技术
I was talking about her sutures.
-小斯隆不能和小格雷搞在一起  -什么
Keep little Sloan out of little Grey is my point. What?
小斯隆不能进入小格雷
Little Sloan does not enter little Grey.
-听清楚了吗  -你刚才说
Are we clear? Did you just say-- Mm-Hmm.
你的话太恶心  而且不准确
Okay, that's just creepy and inaccurate.
是大斯隆
Big Sloan.
正回家吗
You heading home?
我爱你
I love you.
我一直爱着你
I will always love you.
我的心是你的
You own a piece of me.
就算你不在了
So even though you'll be gone,
也会活在我心里
you will never be forgotten, not by me.
很遗憾我们没有机会
I'm sorry we never got our chance.
很遗憾我们没有
I'm sorry we never...
没有结婚生子  一起白头偕老
Got to get married or have children or grow old together.
我一直渴望这些
I wanted that so much.
我最渴望的  就是成为你的妻子
I wanted to be your wife more than anything.
为什么说这些
Why are you telling me this?
我试着放开你  让你安息
I'm trying to let you go so that your soul can be at peace.
我已经安息了  伊兹
But I have peace, Izzie.
我来是为了你
I'm here for you.
再见  丹尼
Good-Bye, Denny.
我爱你
I love you.
但是  再见
But good-Bye.
听我解释
I can explain.
我没教过你们并行缝合法
I did not teach you the parallel pulley stitch.
我自己都很难做到
I can barely do that stitch myself.
不管你们在干什么  马上停止
Whatever you guys are doing, shut it down.
别拿自己来练习  愚不可及
Do not practice on yourselves. That is insane.
马上停止
Shut it down.
伊兹
Iz?
我看到你
I see you.
我一整天都看着你
I've seen you all day.
看着你挣扎
I-I see you struggling.
我知道你不想要我插手  但让我帮你
And I know you don't want my help, but let me help you.
不管是什么事  我能帮你
Whatever it is, I can help.
让我帮你
So let me.
帮我烧掉它好吗
Will you burn this for me?
我恨这种感觉
I hate how hard it is.
就像  你全身心投入
It's just, like, you get attached to someone,
而别人却不领情
And then they work their way into your life,
某天醒来
And then you wake up one day--
突然意识到  脑子里都是他们的...
Suddenly all you can think about is their little...
再来一杯?
Another round?
我去拿
Oh, I'll get it.
告诉我那件事
Tell me the stories.
什么事
What stories?
你不肯让赛迪告诉的那件
The ones you won't let sadie tell me.
陈年往事了
They're ancient history.
丢脸又可笑
Humiliating and ridiculous.
可笑的是一个成熟男性
Ridiculous is a grown man telling another grown
-警告另一位成熟男性  别碰某个女人  -你真的说了
Man to stay out of a woman's little-- You did it?
没错  引用你的原话
I did, those exact words.
我这么做是因为
I did it because...
看到你保护自己的妹妹  我很高兴
It was nice to see you sticking up for your sister.
我这么做是为了你
I did it for you.
所以你欠我
So now you owe me...
一个故事
A story.
好吧
Okay, fine.
但绝不能告诉别人  保证
But you can never tell anyone, ever.
很遗憾没能保住他  那个病人
I'm--I'm sorry we lost him, the patient.
我感到遗憾
I'm--I'm sorry.
不需要你的遗憾
I don't need you to be sorry.
-好吧  -不需要你遗憾
Okay. I don't need you to be sorry.
-好  -我不需要
Okay. I don't need--
-好好好  -我也不需要你
All--All right. All ri-- I don't need you.
人与人之间的联系  说不清道不明
The ties that bind us are sometimes impossible to explain.
有时藕虽断  丝还连
They connect us even after it seems like the ties should be broken.
超越空间
Some bonds defy distance...
超越时间  超越逻辑
And time... and logic...
天啊  我
Oh, god. I...
我已经道别了  我烧掉了毛衣
I said good-Bye. I b-- I burned the sweater.
谢谢你  顺便说一下
Yeah, thanks for that, by the way.
我很喜欢那件毛衣  你给我织的
I love that sweater. You made me that sweater.
-天啊  -停下  别再抓狂了
Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh, my god. Stop freaking out.
-不是真的  不是真的  -我说过
You're not real. You're not real. Hey, I told you...
你不是真的  -我是为你而来的
You're not real. You are not real. I'm here for you.
你不是真的  并不是真的
You are not real. You are not real.
你不是真的
You are not real.
伊兹  看着我
Izzie, look at me.
摸摸我
Touch me.
看到了吗
You see?
我说了我是真的
I told you I was real.
天啊
Oh, god. Hey.
因为有时  这些联系
Because some ties are simply...
早已注定
Meant to be.